最好的朋友
better in stereo
不同的朋友
b-- b-- better in stereo
迎着清晨阳光
- I'm up with the sunshine - let's go
穿上舒服衣裳
- I lace up my high tops - oh no
扣篮  热热身
slam dunk, ready or not
秀出你的份量
yeah, show me what you got
站在舞台中央
- I'm under the spotlight - holler
准备下一场较量
I dare you, come on and follow
你有你的节拍
you dance to your own beat
我的歌声嘹亮
i'll sing the melody
你想接受
when you say yea-ah-ah
我却摇头
I say no-oh-oh
你想停留
when you say stop
我却一心只想  走走走
all I want to do is go go go
你  我最好的朋友
you you, the other half of me me
学不来的朋友
the half i'll never be-e
截然不同的朋友
the half that drives me crazy
你  我最好的朋友
you you, the better half of me me
离不开的朋友
the half i'll always need
你我有
but we both know
不或缺的朋友
we're better in stereo.